SCENES FROM THE PREVIOUS EPISODE
Hello? Yes, this is she.
All right, see you soon.
I have a job interview!
When my father finds out
I'm interviewing to be a secretary,
he'll say,
"Betty, that's not what
you went to college for!"
But if I'm offered the job, I'm taking it.
I'll figure out what to tell him later.
Silence!
Mine is the only voice
we should be hearing.
I'm looking for Human Resources.
Oh, the horror!
That's a very impressive résumé.
Why do you want to be a secretary?
I feel like there's tremendous opportunity
for growth at VandM.
I'm Patricia Fernandez, Marcela's friend.
The one who's applying to be
the president's secretary.
Will you marry me?
Armando proposed to secure
your vote and become president,
that's all.
Armando and I have been together
more than two years.
We're in love.
-You sure there's nobody here?
-Nobody!
If Marcela sees us, she'll kill us.
Who's there?
Get out right now! No, don't!
You can come out now.
What are you doing here?
Open up!
Armando, I know you're in there!
Don't make me call security! Armando!
Armando!
Where's Armando?
This young lady and I
are the only ones in here.
Was there a man here?
No.
Where were you?
What's wrong? Why are you upset?
What'd I do?
Patricia is going to be
your new secretary.
What made you think Patricia Fernandez
could be my secretary?
There's another candidate.
She's actually overqualified.
That's who I want.
She's ugly.
How ugly can she be?
Mr. Mendoza, the other candidate is here.
Send her in.
Ms. Beatriz Aurora Rincon.
You?
Thank you, Smith.
You know each other?
No, of course not.
This is the first time we've met.
This is your résumé?
Pleased to meet you.
You were in the restroom
with Naomi, weren't you?
How do you know her?
I don't.
We just ran into each other
in the restroom.
Hello. How is everyone?
Hi, Dad.
I haven't left yet, and you've
already changed the decor.
You're changing many things, huh?
And this young lady is?
My new secretary.
No, we're in the process
of selecting his new secretary.
Why don't you stay and help us?
I don't need anyone's help
choosing my own secretary, dear.
Why is she in there, and I'm not?
The job was mine. You said so.
Why'd you bring her?
Ms. Fernandez, to Ms. Valencia and I,
you are the ideal candidate,
but the president wanted
to interview that... young lady.
That loser?
How can someone like her
take my job from me?
I mean, look at her!
She has none of my class,
elegance or presence.
Right, Ricky?
Apples and oranges.
I mean,
what's so special about her?
Oh, well, only that she graduated
Summa Cum Laude
with two post-graduate degrees,
a degree in Finance,
and she speaks five languages but...
-Five?
-Five.
All she's missing is an Olympic medal.
No, there's not an athletic bone
in her body.
-Patricia.
-Yeah?
Please join us.
Patricia, please stand
next to this young lady.
Bonjour.
Roberto, these are our two candidates.
Could you wait outside
for a moment, please?
That was low, Marcela.
Dad, Beatriz Rincon is more qualified
than that bimbo Patricia.
Beatriz Aurora Rincon Lozano.
Very interesting.
It's unbelievable how you
could humiliate that poor girl
by making her stand next to your friend.
No, what's unbelievable is you hiring
that insignificant woman
for a job that requires
elegance and social skills.
We're a fashion house.
Your secretary should represent
the company.
Isn't that right, Roberto?
I doubt he'll disregard
someone's skill set
in favor of their image, right, Dad?
You're both right.
Patricia is elegant,
sociable and distinguished.
And this young lady, Beatriz,
has an impressive résumé
and appears to be efficient.
Why not hire them both
on a one-month trial period?
You can decide who stays after that.
Hello, Mr. Valencia.
Don't be an idiot.
If you were a spy, you'd be dead.
-What do you have for me?
-Sorry, sir.
This is Mendoza's business plan.
All of its mistakes are underlined in red.
If he goes through with the plan,
we'll have serious financial
troubles within six months.
And you know what else?
He won't meet his goal.
Good job, Mata.
I'll present this report
at our next meeting
before Roberto leaves the country.
My sister has to wake up
and see who that man really is.
Don't worry.
Armando is his own worst enemy.
The company was very chaotic this morning.
There was so much noise...
Mata! What happened?
I was in the lobby when I noticed
your sister looking very tense.
She was arguing with Wilson.
There's a model locked in the bathroom.
I need the keys! Give them to me!
It's the master key.
I'm not authorized to give them to you.
It's an order!
I can go with you to open the door.
Let's go!
I don't know what happened afterward.
She was tense, but also upset,
angry, annoyed...
Mata!
Like when Armando was found
with that model.
Remember her?
That dark, long-haired beauty?
Mata, here's what we'll do:
Find out which model was in the restroom,
and watch Armando.
I'll do some digging of my own.
Marce, thank you for treating me
to a massage.
I really needed it. I'm very stressed out.
I don't know how I'm going to put up
with that scarecrow in the office.
I know. Don't even bring her up.
I don't like that woman. She's dangerous.
Look, don't worry.
Beatriz won't last long at VandM.
I'll take bug spray to work
tomorrow and get rid of her.
But Marce... You know my situation.
Don't start, Patricia.
I already gave you a one-week advance.
And don't you dare
tell the other secretaries
how much you earn,
which is much more than they do.
-I'm not a secretary.
-Whatever.
Hi, Patricia. It's Daniel Valencia.
Let's have dinner.
No one needs to know, you know?
I know that smile. Who is it?
Stop it!
-You won't tell me who it is?
-No.
I have to get ready.
Yes! What do I wear?
Oh, Marce.
-You going to eat that?
-Don't! Of course I am!
You're so stingy!
It's your first time
beating the pretty girl.
That calls for a celebration!
Let's get beers or a bottle!
There's nothing to celebrate.
I didn't beat anyone.
We're competing to see who gets the job.
And as always happens, it'll probably be
that Patricia Fernandez.
Quit being so pessimistic.
Send the pessimism away.
If we strip away the glamour,
luxury and the models,
VandM is just a company that needs
to make money to survive.
What are you good at?
Don't make me go deaf, Betty!
Make that your mantra.
You have to believe it.
Yes, Betty.
-Know what else gives me hope?
-What?
Mr. Armando, the son of VandM's owner,
defended me in front of his girlfriend.
I'm sure he wants me
to stay at the company.
And you will, Betty.
So what's the scoop?
You were in the bathroom
and Naomi was with your boss
and you caught them red-handed?
Please tell me more!
Super red-handed!
I was in the stall,
and Naomi and Armando were outside.
Then his fiancée showed up.
I'm sure Naomi will never
set foot in VandM again.
Why didn't you call or FaceTime me?
I wanted to see her. You know I love her!
She's my Aphrodite!
You're such a bad friend!
Quit acting like
a horny old coot, Nicolas!
"She's my Aphrodite!"
Well, she arouses me. Is that so bad?
Nicolas!
Hello, Armando. How are you?
I'm well.
Does this mean you agree to be part
of my fashion show?
I'm dying to work with Shannon De Lima.
Maybe.
Hey, hey. Are you leaving just like that?
-Huh?
-Already?
You have my answer. Maybe.
I wanted to congratulate you
on your new job at VandM.
You're Armando Mendoza's
executive secretary.
You really know how to make
the most of your connections.
Thank you, Daniel.
I'm thrilled you asked me out to dinner.
Now we can get to know each other better.
Don't congratulate me just yet, though.
Armando hired another secretary.
He did? Why does he need two?
Is he so inept
he can't manage with just one?
What can I say?
That's Armando for you.
It's obvious he isn't ready
to be president.
Plus, he also dates the models
that work for VandM.
You're telling me.
Poor Marce!
She's been through so much
because of his infidelities.
Today she thought Armando
had locked himself in a restroom
with one of the models.
Really? Who?
The same one as last year.
The one that caused
the social media scandal.
But that man could be anyone.
Oh, I don't know.
Marce swears it's Armando.
Naomi Ferretti is a menace.
Why else would Marce bar her from VandM?
Those two are mortal enemies.
Patricia, you'll answer the phone,
welcome guests,
take them to the conference room,
handle the catering
and deliver my mail.
Yes, I know how to do all that very well.
Beatriz, you'll be my voice
within the company.
You'll speak to the accountants,
administrators,
and handle all fiscal affairs.
Yes.
Sorry, Armand,
but I think you're forgetting
that I studied finance
for three semesters at TUI.
Oh, yes.
First, prove you're capable of handling
everything I asked of you.
Or did you want to take over
Betty's tasks, as well?
Betty, I'll also want reports
on our bank accounts and suppliers.
I'll remind both of you
that you're on a probationary period.
OK, so I'm going to need your passwords.
The ones for your electronic
devices, cell phone, laptop...
so I can manage your agenda.
That's not your job.
Beatriz, you'll manage my personal agenda.
-But...
-No buts.
I don't want to hear your voice
unless it's to transfer a call.
Get to work, you two.
Your desk is outside, Patricia.
Over there?
Yes, out there.
Beatriz, hang back a moment
so I can show you where you'll be working.
Thank you.
Marce! Marce!
What's the matter? What's wrong?
Your fiancé is so annoying!
He put that hideous monster above me.
He kept her in his office
and kicked me out.
Here's a word of advice.
Today's your first day on the job.
Quit complaining and smile.
Quit complaining and smile?
Perfect, Marcela!
Let me tell you about my job description.
I'm going to answer the phone,
answer emails and serve coffee.
While in the meantime, that mustached uggo
gets to know all of Armando's passwords.
She's going to manage his personal agenda.
She is?
She's going to cover for him.
It's all good, though.
I'll smile and won't complain one bit.
Everything's perfect
in this clueless office.
Come in.
This is it.
I know it's not great,
but this is the only space available.
I wasn't planning
on hiring two secretaries.
Come in.
Thank you.
If you're not comfortable here,
I'll assign you a spot in
the production or design area.
No, don't worry. This is fine.
It's best to stay close
so we can communicate directly.
Sure. I read in your résumé
that you're a very good financial analyst.
Here.
This is the business plan
I presented at the meeting.
What do you want me to do with it?
I want a finance expert to analyze it.
Give me your honest opinion.
Sure. Of course. It'd be my pleasure.
I also wanted to thank you
for what you did for me.
In the restroom.
I really appreciate your loyalty.
Armando!
Excuse me.
Why can't Patricia manage your agenda?
Because I don't want her to. Beatriz will.
You'd rather let a complete stranger
manage your personal information?
Someone so insignificant
and with such poor taste
is going to plan
a fashion company's events?
-Stop!
-What?
-Lower your voice!
-It's the truth.
It's not Beatriz that's bothering you.
You're annoyed
I didn't give your friend access
-to my personal life.
-Nonsense.
-You are.
-And what if I were?
-Do you have anything to hide?
-No.
You promised you'd change
when you proposed
and that I'd never have to worry
about you cheating.
And last night you said
you'd make an effort
to trust me more.
What happened to that?
Beatriz will manage my agenda
whether you like it or not.
I just hope she's not
one of your co-conspirators.
If I find out Beatriz is covering for you,
I'll fire her on the spot.
OK.
Hello.
Do any of you know
where I can heat up my food?
In the break room.
But since today's your first day,
the Squad would like to invite you
to have lunch with us.
Thanks, but my mom packed my lunch.
I said "invite" because
we all bring our lunch
and eat it together.
It's tastier that way.
We want to spend time with you
and welcome you to VandM.
And we also want to know
why there are two secretaries.
That's never happened before.
Hold on.
We don't even know
if she wants to be our friend.
I do.
Yeah!
I'm Betty. Hello.
Nice to meet you. I'm Bertha.
I'm Sofia.
Hi, Betty. I'm Aura Maria.
Sandra.
And I'm Mariana. Nice to meet you.
It's very nice to meet all of you.
Hello. We're going to lunch.
You're welcome to join us
so we can get to know each other.
You're so funny.
Why would I want to get to know you?
She's so funny.
Why are you laughing?
What do you mean, Marce?
These girls are so out of touch.
I told you that if you made me
a secretary,
they'd think I was one of them.
-Shall we go have lunch?
-Yes, please!
Hey... so why do you
call yourselves the Squad?
Oh, I can tell you why.
Mr. Hugo Lombardi gave us
the nickname the Ugly Battalion.
We renamed ourselves
the Unconventional Beauties Squad.
Beauty is relative, isn't it?
As you can see, we're all smart,
pretty, and hot.
People say the perfect woman
should be 36-24-36,
but even if some of us
are 36-24-infinity...
Not all of us!
But we're still amazing!
Betty, we have a question.
Since our dear
and charming friend Patricia
is going to be working
at Carmencita's desk,
where will you be working?
In the office right next
to the president's office.
Oh!
What? No!
No, no!
You're working in that dump? No way!
You're definitely one of us.
Welcome to VandM and the Squad.
Welcome! Betty, I have a question.
Did your boss tell you
when he plans to get married?
That hunk is a true alpha male.
Did you hear about the scandal
of the blacklisted model?
-Yes.
-Yeah?
No, no.
-You didn't?
-No.
-Did you or did you not?
-Want me to fill you in?
-Yeah.
I'm up to speed on everything.
It seems Marcela hates a model
by the name of Naomi Ferretti.
Her name cannot be spoken.
But an error was made
during the hiring process.
Naomi?
Come closer. I've been expecting you.
I asked you to meet me here.
My agent said I was--
Going to a job?
I'm paying you for your time.
This is what you'd earn in a day
during Fashion Week.
It's a pleasure to meet you.
Daniel Valencia.
-Valencia?
-Uh-huh.
-As in Valencia from VandM?
-Yes, that's right.
I can't believe Marcela
would stoop so low.
Hey, hey. Calm down.
Marcela didn't send me.
I sought you out
because I don't want her
to marry Armando Mendoza.
And if I'm not mistaken, you don't either.
Armando is lying to my sister,
and I need you to tell me
the nature of your relationship.
That's all.
I'm a model, not an informant,
Mr. Valencia.
All right. Here's what we'll do.
Naomi, you and I can stop Armando Mendoza.
Think about it.
You have the passwords
to all of my devices.
Please be very discreet.
No one can know those.
Not even Marcela.
Don't worry.
I'm keeping them
in my password manager app.
They'll have to pry that information
from my cold dead hands.
I'm not kidding. This is serious.
Sorry, sir.
Everyone here is doing everything they can
to make sure the show is perfect.
This is why it's so important
that you manage my information.
Yeah.
I'm getting married,
and I'm changing my ways.
I really want to be a better man.
So...
Baby, I'm at Le Blanc.
If you don't show up in half an hour,
I'll go looking for you at the office.
I have to go.
Go to the office and tell everyone
I'm meeting with O'Brian
from Sportification.
Understood. I'm at your service.
Yes.
-No!
-It's a secret.
Sorry, sorry. I have what you requested.
We wasted a lot of time
because of you, child.
The world moved on, and we did, too.
Where's Armando?
He's not answering my calls.
Mr. Armando had a bit of a problem
with his agenda.
It's just that--
It's just that If I were
managing his schedule,
everything would be
running like clockwork.
When I was at TUI University,
I was a whiz at advanced
organizational patterns.
NASA uses that technology, too.
-That's not it.
-Back talking, too?
Tell me, has a spacecraft ever been late
when landing on the moon?
Kid, we just want to know
why Mr. Armando Mendoza
isn't here meeting with us?
I'm trying to tell you,
but you're not letting me.
-What?
-Sorry, sorry.
Mr. Armando received
an urgent call from Mr. O'Brian,
from Sportification,
and they're meeting about work.
Beatriz, what are you hiding from us?
Nothing.
Nothing?
-No.
-No?
Mr. O'Brian is on vacation.
Oops!
Busted!
Beatriz, tell me where Armando is.
It's over, Naomi.
And this time, I mean it.
No, Armando.
It'll never be over between us.
Come closer.
That's what I like about us.
We make no promises,
and we've lasted longer than most couples.
Listen, you're out of your mind.
I'm going to marry Marcela,
and she's the only woman for me.
Oh, please! You're a terrible liar.
If it were someone else, I'd believe you.
Marcela?
All of Manhattan knows
she's just a business decision for you.
You're free to think whatever you want,
but please don't seek me out again.
And if I refuse?
I'll have to treat you like what you are.
A lunatic.
A lunatic?
You wouldn't.
It'd be a scandal.
All right.
This isn't over. Get back here.
-Armando.
-Margot!
How are you?
I'm well. Thank you.
I heard you're getting married.
-I am.
-Congratulations.
-Thank you.
-Is Marcela with you?
She should be here soon.
I'm in a rush, so I won't get
to congratulate her in person,
but please say hi to her for me.
-Sure.
-It was nice seeing you.
Likewise. Bye.
Don't seek me out again.
If you do, I'll call the police
and file a restraining order against you.
End of story.
Excuse me.
Yes, Beatriz?
Something very serious happened, sir.
Ms. Marcela says Mr. O'Brian is traveling,
and she demands to speak with you.
I'll call the office in five minutes.
I need to come up with an excuse.
OK, but please hurry. She's furious!
Beatriz, did you get a hold of Armando?
I'm on it!
Daniel Valencia?
Marce, let Armando speak first,
so he'll dig his own grave.
Of course not!
Men love to say "I love you"
to get you to fall for it.
M-M-Miss M-M-Marcela...
I spoke with Mr. Armando.
The connection wasn't great
so I couldn't make out what he was saying,
but he said he'd call you soon.
Lies upon lies.
Was he with Mr. O'Brian?
Y-y-yes.
Then we'll call him
and he'll put Armando on the line.
How are you?
I'm well. I'm sorry to bother you,
but I heard you had a last-minute meeting
with Armando.
Is everything OK?
Is everything OK
with the company, with life?
I owe you one!
-Ladykillers!
How was your first day on the job, Betty?
Really bad.
Mr. Armando asked me to cover
for him again and I did.
I know I can be so much more
than a secretary.
I can offer the company so much more.
Oh, yeah? Like what?
This is the business plan Mr. Armando
presented to win the presidency.
There are a few mistakes,
but they can be corrected.
I went through it,
and I'll make some suggestions.
And you're making a little extra
for doing this?
No.
That's not why I'm doing it, though.
I want Mr. Armando to know
that he can trust me.
He needs a right-hand person.
What if he's a lefty?
Then I'll be his left-hand person.
I want him to know he can trust me.
A company president needs a right hand.
They're indispensable.
You were checking up on me, weren't you?
Why else would you call O'Brian?
Because I thought
he was still on vacation.
I had my assistant give you a message,
and you didn't believe either of us.
We've had a lot of problems
because you've lied to me about women.
-That's not true.
-Yes, it is!
If going to a meeting leads to this mess,
what will the future hold for us?
Do I have to inform you
of every move I make?
OK. I'm sorry, OK?
I'm under a lot of pressure,
and you're not helping.
I have to answer to my family,
I have to oversee the business
and plan the wedding.
I swear I will.
It'll be this year, I promise.
-Know what would be nice?
-What?
If you announced our engagement
at your dad's going away party.
What? Do you regret it?
No, of course not.
I just want you to know that I love you.
And don't you forget it.
You think Naomi will leave you alone?
She can get upset or get over it.
Hello, Mr. Armando.
Hi, Betty. Good morning.
Let me introduce you.
This is Beatriz Rincon,
my personal assistant.
Ricardo Calderon,
VP of Business Management
and minority shareholder.
He's also a friend.
I trust him wholeheartedly.
Nice to meet you, Mr. Ricardo.
Personal assistant?
The pleasure is all mine.
Well, I'll be in my cubicle.
OK.
You're keeping her in the storage room?
I had to put her somewhere.
Where else would she go?
Outside, with the rest of the gargoyles!
She's very efficient.
At getting rid of evil spirits.
Please think this through.
If you agree to do this,
it'll be harder to leave Marcela.
I already planned the after-party.
You have no idea how many babes
are coming.
All right, I'll just say one thing.
Do you really have to make
the announcement today?
Yes. It's happening.
I can't believe it. We should be mourning.
Do you think I can handle
that after-party by myself?
Shut up. Here they come.
You can do it tomorrow.
It doesn't have to be today.
Zip it.
Auntie, you look beautiful, as always.
-Thank you.
-You're welcome.
Hi.
-Uncle.
-Hi.
-Today's the today.
-This all looks great.
-We are so proud of you.
-Thank you.
Let's hope this isn't VandM's
last big runway show.
Always the well-wisher.
But I'll remind you
that this is your company, too.
You'd benefit from us doing well.
And I'll remind you
that both of our families' fortunes
are in your hands.
I'll remind both of you of where we are.
Behave accordingly. Like adults!
I agree.
Dani, let's get a drink and mingle.
I have to greet some important people.
OK.
Roberto, Margarita,
when I look at you, my eyes water.
We're really going to miss you very much.
Your absence will be felt.
You have no idea what your son
has planned for VandM.
We're working on a new casual,
ready-to-wear line.
My line sheet! Your dad has to see it.
I don't have it with me.
It's in my office.
Don't worry, though.
I'll have it brought over.
Betty.
The taxi will be here soon.
This is so exciting.
I'd love to attend an event like that.
I bet there are lots
of beautiful, elegant people
and so many hot men.
You can come with me if you like.
-Sure.
-We can't.
Only executives are allowed.
Mariana gets to go because she handles
the social media stuff.
We don't. That sucks.
It's here. Bye.
Betty, one more thing.
I peeked at the menu,
and everything looks delicious.
If you're allowed to have food,
bring some for us.
Yes, sure.
Don't forget to photograph the hotties.
Send the pictures to our group chat.
OK, bye.
Is your dad coming?
I don't think so.
Too many issues at the office.
-Yeah?
-Yeah.
Hello.
Hi, Roberto.
Congratulations.
You've left your son a wonderful legacy.
I feel good about retiring
because the company is in good hands.
I hope my dad is just as proud
when it's my turn to take over.
He will be. You'll see.
Trust him.
-Tiffany, it's so nice to see you.
-Hi.
I have to steal him away.
You're wanted for an interview.
-Again?
-Come on.
Well, duty calls.
Enjoy.
Thank you.
-Know what I'm going to do?
-What?
I'm going to invite your father
to a game of golf.
He'll be thrilled.
-Yeah?
-Yeah. Of course.
What are you doing there? Get inside!
I'm trying, but the hall monitor
won't let me through.
-Thank you!
-Come on.
Thank you so much.
Mr. Armando asked me to deliver
these to Hugo immediately.
Go on, then. He's waiting for you.
Naomi!
Mr. Armando is a dead man.
No, we can keep Ms. Marcela
from seeing her.
I'll keep her busy, and you keep her
away from Mr. Armando.
Good afternoon, everyone.
Welcome to VandM's new collection launch.
We chose this beautiful set as a backdrop
to honor a man who has dedicated
more than 30 years
to the world of fashion.
My father, Roberto Mendoza.
Welcome all! Enjoy VandM's new collection.
Naomi!
No, no, no!
Don't!
What is that woman doing here?
She came to bring Hugo's sketchbook.
-On the runway?
-She was looking for me.
Quit making excuses for her.
She made a mess of everything!
This was a hit!
What are you talking about?
Didn't you see when she threw herself
on the runway?
People are staring. Please smile.
Thanks!
Could I have a moment of your time?
Sure.
What are you doing here?
I said it was over between us.
You were very clear.
I'm here for Marcela, not you.
Don't drag Marcela into this.
You dragged her into this
when you proposed to her.
She deserves to know
the type of man she's marrying.
You want to talk to her and ruin my life?
I'll take you to her so you can
tell her everything about us.
-Come on.
-You think I won't?
Oh, I know you will.
I'll take you to her so you can talk,
and then you can forget
about your modeling career
because I'll call every agency, magazine
and fashion house and you'll never model
so much as oven mitts again!
You're not that powerful.
Try me!
I won't let some lunatic,
some psycho ruin my life.
You're a bastard!
I swear you'll pay for each
and every woman you've hurt.
Stop! Isn't that Naomi?
It is. What is she doing here?
Let's find out.
-Marcelita, darling.
-How are you, Margot?
-Hi, Patricia.
-Hi.
Everything turned out so nice.
Not even that tiny hiccup
could ruin the show.
-Congratulations!
-Thank you!
By the way, I saw Armando
at a restaurant yesterday.
What? Yesterday?
Yes.
-Are you sure it was him?
-Yes.
I asked about you,
and he said you were on your way.
He was with a model that'd worked for you.
What's her name? Noemi?
Naomi.
Yes, her.
Mariana, I ruined Mr. Armando's
first runway show.
I bet he hates me right now.
It was an accident, Betty.
Give it some time
and everyone will have forgotten.
Where is she?
How dare you remain here
after what you did?
Days and nights of work
ruined because of you!
You're a destroyer of aesthetics
and beauty!
What the hell are you doing here?
Sorry, sorry! It was an accident!
Your birth was an accident.
Will removing the hideous rags
you call clothes
and using them to drown you
qualify as an accident, too?
Ugly people should die! Get out!
-Calm down.
-Don't.
You know what I'm like when I'm like this.
Yes, yes...
I'll never set foot... Listen to me.
I'll never set foot in VandM again.
This was my last runway show.
Leave me alone. Give me some space.
Are you deaf? Leave the planet!
Go!
Betty!
You really lucked out.
Had Naomi spoken to Marcela...
Nothing would've happened.
It would've been her word against mine.
-What?
-Yes.
We live in the era of social media.
Never in the history of male infidelity
have we been so...
so watched.
We're cornered.
I've been backed into a corner
due to Betty's mishap.
We're getting off on the wrong foot.
If Betty had been just a little prettier,
it would've been different.
You know people like beauty.
No, that's not it, but I think
hiring her was a mistake.
I'll have to fire her.
-Mr. Armando.
-Not now, Mariana.
I hope Hugo doesn't get
in one of his moods.
-Fat chance!
-Mr. Armando.
Not now! What is it?
I have to talk to you.
It's very important.
-It can't wait.
-What is it?
What do you think you're doing?
Picking up Mr. Hugo's designs.
It's called a line sheet.
You must mean what's left of the work
of one of the company's top designers.
The horror! You're so ugly.
Why don't you quit, Ugly Betty?
No one will want you
at VandM tomorrow anyway.
It was an accident.
Yes, you're an accident.
An accident I'm grateful for.
I'll get to be Armand's assistant now.
Don't be sad.
It's not my fault.
Some people are born to shine
and others, like you, are meant
to watch us shine from below.
Hi, Dad.
Hi, sweetie.
Guess what?
I gave the attorney his retainer.
He's expensive,
but paying his fees will be worth it
now that you're helping me.
How expensive?
Not as expensive as I initially thought.
He advertises his services on TV all day.
I'm feeling very optimistic.
Look! That's him!
That's Peter!
Oh, my. You think he's any good?
Of course he is.
If he weren't, he wouldn't be on TV.
-Yeah.
-What's wrong? You seem down.
Did something happen today?
Just adapting to the new job.
I know the first days are hard.
I went through it when I went
from a janitor in night school
to the office accountant.
But you know what? It'll be OK.
Tomorrow will always be a better day.
Take it from your dad that loves you.
And I you.
Do you watch this series?
I really appreciate your help.
Yes, please be very discreet.
Whatever you want. You're so sweet.
Thank you!
If you didn't want the phone,
you could've given it to me!
He lied to me, Patricia!
He wasn't at a business meeting!
He was with that slut at Le Blanc!
The restaurant manager just confirmed it.
And Uggo was probably covering for him.
That's why she caused that scene
during the fashion show.
So you wouldn't realize Naomi was there.
Shut up! Don't remind me!
Armando forgot to announce
our engagement because of her!
Now I get why Armando hired her.
To be his accomplice!
You poor thing.
They're making a fool of you.
I imagine you're going
to confront Armando.
No, Patricia!
I'll handle the bigger issue here.
Oh!
Don't worry, Mariana. I'll be fine.
I was really worried about you yesterday.
You looked so sad and upset.
Of course I was.
I ruined Mr. Armando's and Hugo's big day.
I bet they hate me right now.
I doubt it.
Mr. Armando can be surly
and a bit of a dictator,
but he's a good person. He'll understand.
But Hugo...
Good morning, Ms. Marcela.
Spare me the greeting
and gather your things.
It was worse.